<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Composite//EN" "ditabase.dtd">
<concept xmlns:ditaarch="http://dita.oasis-open.org/architecture/2005/" id="DARS_11.101" ditaarch:DITAArchVersion="1.3">
   <title outputclass="Heading 3">
      <ph props="autonumber">11.101</ph> Order of precedence for requirements documents.</title>
   <conbody>
      <p id="GSBOwB" outputclass="Text Body">(S-90) Submission of Information Technology, Cyber and Telecommunications Requirements.</p>
      <p id="wmvzGA" outputclass="List1">(1) Requirements for hardware, software, services, networks and systems (including telecommunications) that require an acquisition package (e.g., SOW/SOO/PWS, equipment/material list, QASP, evaluation plan) shall be submitted in accordance with the DITCO Information Technology &amp; Telecommunications Acquisition Package Submission &amp; Ordering Guide website at<xref format="asp" href="https://www.ditco.disa.mil/contracts/IT_instruct.asp" scope="external">
            <u>https://www.ditco.disa.mil/contracts/IT_instruct.asp</u>.</xref> TSRs/TSOs and PDCs are not authorized funding documents for procurement actions requiring acquisition packages.</p>
      <p id="aQRdYs" outputclass="List1">(2) Requirements for individual telecommunication circuits (including integrated equipment, installation, and maintenance), long haul telecommunications services satisfied via the Public Switched Telephone Network (PSTN), commercial internet services, wireless telecommunication services (e.g., cell phones, satellite communications equipment) and pre-priced telecommunication services/equipment requirements available under existing Indefinite Delivery (ID) contract vehicles shall be submitted to DITCO via the DISA Storefront (DSF) application at <xref format="html" href="https://disa-storefront.disa.mil/dsf/sfoverview" scope="external">
            <u>https://disa-storefront.disa.mil/dsf/sfoverview</u>.</xref> Telecommunication Service Requests/Telecommunications Service Orders (TSR/TSO) with valid Product Description Codes (PDC) are the only authorized customer requirements and funding documents for the aforementioned telecommunications requirements.</p>
      <p id="p_211.274" outputclass="Normal"></p>
   </conbody>
</concept>
